[
    {
        "id"          : "1",          
        "question"    : "Statues of Buddha show him sitting on ...?",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "a"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "2",          
        "question"    : "The owl and the pussycat bought their wedding ring from which animal?",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "b"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "3",          
        "question"    : "Four cards of a straight in poker with a card in the middle missing is called ?",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "b"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "4",          
        "question"    : "Who played at the Stadio Delle Alpi until 2006?",
        "answer_a"    : "Real Betis",
        "answer_b"    : "AC Milan",
        "answer_c"    : "Sampdoria",
        "answer_d"    : "Juventus",
        "correct"     : "d"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "5",          
        "question"    : "Which of the following words does not contain all the vowels?",
        "answer_a"    : "Facetious",
        "answer_b"    : "Abstemious",
        "answer_c"    : "Insouciant",
        "answer_d"    : "Uncomplimentary",
        "correct"     : "c"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "6",          
        "question"    : "xasxasxasWhat is you're name 2?",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "b"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "7",          
        "question"    : "xasxasxasWhat is you're name 2?",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "b"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "8",          
        "question"    : "asdasdsadsadsadasdasd ??",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "a"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "9",          
        "question"    : "What is you're name 2?",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "b"
    },
    {
        "id"          : "10",          
        "question"    : "xasxasxasWhat is you're name 2?",
        "answer_a"    : "awais",
        "answer_b"    : "awais1",
        "answer_c"    : "awais2",
        "answer_d"    : "awais3",
        "correct"     : "b"
    }
]
